我是杰森.西弗，是个心理医生
Hi. I'm Jason Seaver. I'm a psychiatrist.
过去15年里 我致力于解决患者的问题
I've spent the last 15 years helping people with their problems.
我是麦姬.西弗
And I'm Maggie Seaver.
过去15年里，我一直围着孩子们转
I've spent the last 15 years helping our kids...
解决那些杰森也束手无策的问题
with problems even Jason wouldn't believe.
现在麦姬已重操旧业 在一家当地报社做记者
Now Maggie has gone back to work as a reporter for the local newspaper.
杰森把他的诊所搬到了家里 这样就可以陪着孩子们了
And Jason has moved his practice into the house so we can be there for the kids.
-他们是可爱的孩子 -大多时候都是
- They're great kids. - Most of the time.
但是有时…
And the rest of the time....
-但是我们爱他们 -是的
- We love them, anyway. - Yeah.
鬼才相信
Unbelievable.
(English Subtitle) Growing.Pains.S01E02 -= Springsteen =- Subripped by zerox
斯普林斯丁的演唱会门票终于来了
This is it, my Springsteen tickets.
喂
Hello?
他们什么时候才会讨厌溜冰板？
When do they outgrow skateboards?
等你送他们架相机后
When you buy them a Camaro.
对，好的
Yeah, okay.
拜
Bye.
要去听演唱会了是吗？
Gonna see Springsteen, huh?
对，明天晚上，肯定很精彩
Yep. Tomorrow night. It's gonna be awesome.
女士们先生们…
Ladies and gentlemen...
演出开始
the Boss.
我还以为演唱会的票 一早卖光了呢
Wait, wait. I thought the Springsteen concert was sold-out.
卖光了？
Sold-out?
凯罗，对门路多的人来说 什么买不到？
Carol, to a man with connections, nothing is ever sold-out.
刚才打电话来的是塞斯.詹姆森
That just happened to be Seth Jameson...
他叔叔的小舅子在体育馆里面…
nephew of the man whose brother-in-law owns a hot-dog concession...
有个卖小吃的摊位
at the Coliseum.
哇哦
Wow.
那你弄到票没？
So did you get tickets?
弄到票没？当然弄到啦
Did I get tickets? Of course l got tickets.
是吗？斯普林斯丁演唱会的门票？
You did? To Springsteen?
不
Well, no.
去喝冰酸梅汤…
To the Ice Capades...
那的座位很舒服
but I got very good seats...
还免费送两个热狗
and two free hot dogs.
讲到门路关系 那么热狗是纯牛肉的吗？
Talk about connections. Are those all-beef dogs?
音乐会的门票那么难搞 你一定很失望吧
It's too bad about the concert, honey. You must be disappointed.
不，办法有的是，票我准能弄到
No, I actually got a couple of other things going. Ill get the tickets.
你们看，办法来了
All right. This is it.
喂？
Hello?
对，你说吧
Yeah. Talk to me.
是的
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
回头再说
Yeah, Ill see you.
又没戏？
No dice?
杰里说他朋友蛐蛐儿准能 帮我们弄到票的…
No. Jerry was sure he'd be able to get those tickets from his friend Cheech, but--
蛐蛐儿？
Cheech?
杰森，他竟然认识个叫蛐蛐儿的人
Jason, our son knows people named Cheech?
麦姬，怎么能凭名字来判断一个人呢
Maggie, you cant judge somebody on the basis of a name.
麦克，你往下说
Anyway, Mike, you were saying?
蛐蛐儿都快被判刑了 可他还在倒卖票子
Yeah, well, Cheech's parole officer didn't think it'd be such a good idea for him...
蛐蛐儿的假释监护人认为这样不好
to be scalping tickets so close to the trial.
你可真有眼力，蛐蛐儿
Good judgment, there, Cheech.
太遗憾了，宝贝
Were sorry, honey.
没关系
That's all right.
办法嘛，我总会有的
I still got one more shot.
小吉，我是麦克
Hey, Jimski. Yeah, it's Mike.
听我说，我一定要搞到一张票子
Yeah. Look, I gotta have those tickets.
对，他想要什么都可以
Yes. Look, offer them anything they want.
什么？
What?
我的夹克衫
My jacket?
我的皮夹克？ 真正小牛皮做的那件夹克？
My leather jacket? The one that smells like actual cattle?
他送了两年的报纸才买了那件夹克 他喜欢那件衣服
He delivered papers for two years to get that jacket. He loves that jacket.
连我都喜欢
I love that jacket.
这么高级的衣服我都没穿过
Of course, I never had a jacket that nice.
好吧，夹克衫可以给他
Okay, okay, he can have the jacket.
拜托啦，吉米…
Oh, come on. Jimmy....
这话我很难跟杰里说出口的
Look, I hate to even ask Jerry that.
好吧，我等你电话
Yeah, all right. Look, call me right back.
他们想跟杰里的妹妹约会
He wanted a date with Jerry's sister.
翠茜？
Trixie?
她才11岁啊
She's only 11.
我说了不行
I said no.
麦克，那件夹克衫你真的愿、意让出去？
Say, Mike, you don't really want to part with that jacket, do you?
不，可是爸爸，这场演唱会…
No, but, Dad, there's no way that Bruce...
就在我们家不远的地方举办 我不想错过
is gonna play 10 miles from my house, and I'm gonna miss him.
我一定要去听一场
Dad, I gotta go to that concert.
-又来了 -喂
- There it is. - Yep.
什么？
What?
这怎么行呢
That's impossible.
是的
Yeah.
好吧，再见
Okay. See you.
怎么了？
Well?
-有人用房子换票子 -用房子？
- Somebody offered him a house. - A house?
对，他们想度个周末 可我们办不到
Well, it was just for a weekend, but that's still out of our league.
-除非… -麦克
- Unless.... - Mike.
好吧，那算了
Okay. Fine.
麦克，这至少能保住那件夹克对吗？
Hey, Mike, at least you still have that jacket, right?
管它呢，闻起来一股死牛味
Who cares? It smells like a dead cow.
妈妈…我看见楼上有只大老鼠
Mom, Mom, Mom. I just saw a mouse in the attic this big.
它究竟是老鼠还是小羊？
Was this a mouse or a small sheep?
它长着贼溜溜的眼睛 长尾巴，走起路来就像这样
Well, it had beady little eyes and a long tail, and went like this.
那是羊，没错
That's a sheep, all right.
好吧，我的老鼠夹放哪去了？
Okay, okay. Where did I put those mousetraps?
你找老鼠夹干嘛，妈妈？
What are you gonna do with the mousetraps, Mom?
老实跟你说吧，凯罗 我打算用它来夹老鼠
Well, Ill be honest with you, Carol, I plan to use them to trap mice.
-会把老鼠夹死吗？ -但愿、如此
- Wont that kill them? - Hopefully.
妈妈
Mom.
凯罗，当妈的就该做好 自己的份内事
Carol, a mom's gotta do what a mom's gotta do.
儿子，把奶酪给我拿来
Son, bring me my Camembert.
好极了，老鼠一定会上钩的
All right. Were going with the big guns.
妈妈，老鼠是个聪明无害的动物啊
Well, Mom, I mean, they're cute, harmless little creatures.
凯罗，十世纪的时候，就是老鼠…
Carol, these are the same guys who carried the plague all through Europe...
让瘟疫传遍整个欧洲 害死了数千万人
during the 10th century and killed millions of people.
那是一千年前的事了，妈妈
That was 1,000 years ago, Mom.
你难道还不能原谅它吗？
How long are you going to hold a grudge?
麦克
Michael.
来吧
Go ahead. Try it.
你帮我想一个活下去的理由吧，妈妈
Try to give me one good reason to go on living, Mom.
来个摇滚歌星舞会
The Solid Gold dancers.
可惜爸爸不在家
Well, at least Dads not here.
他倒是会帮我驱散我的烦恼
I mean, he'd really try to cheer me up.
他是个滑头
The slime.
他装得好像一直都很同情我
I mean, he always acts like he's gonna be real sympathetic...
然后他会一下子跟你说…
and then before you know it, he turns on you:
“麦克…”
"Mike, Mike, Mike.
“我认为在这种情况下…”
"l find that at times like these...
“对生活你最好还是要往前看”
"it's always best to keep a little perspective on life."
至少他从没对你说过…
At least he didn't give you that line...
他像你这么大时有什么苦闷
about how rough he had it when he was your age.
确实没有，他常说…
No, no. That's right. He always says:
“麦克…”
"Mike...
“我不想跟你谈我在你这么大时 有多么苦闷…”
"lm not gonna give you that line about how rough I had it when l was your age...
“但你要知道从历史上来看…”
"but I think that you should be aware...
“比你苦闷的人多着呢”
"that historically, people have had it rougher than this."
-嗨 -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
家里有老鼠吗？
Do we have mice?
是的
Yep...
如果我24小时还不回来…
and if I'm not back in 24 hours...
你就买只猫吧
call a cat.
麦克…
Mike, Mike, Mike.
情绪仍然不好吗，小伙子？
Still feeling pretty low, huh, pal?
我很好，老爸 别谈这个，好吗？
Dad, I'm feeling fine. Let's just drop it, okay?
别这样嘛，我明白你现在的心情
Come on, come on. I know what you're going through.
-那当然 -我真的明白
- Yeah, sure, Dad. - No, I do. l really do.
今早怕你不开心，所以我才没说
You know, I didn't want to bring it up this morning and depress you...
我听过斯普林斯丁的演唱会
but I have seen Springsteen in concert.
你听过？
You have?
十年前吧
Ten years ago.
-是吗？感觉如何？ -棒极了
- Really? What was it like? - Amazing.
他的音乐简直能把门都震破
I mean, the guy completely blows your doors off.
-够了，我不想听这个 -他简直让我…
- God, I don't want to hear this. - He made me feel so...
-行了，老爸 -解脱
- Please, Dad. - ... free.
当时我走出演唱会现场…
I could have just walked out of that concert...
差点能搭便车周游全国
and hitchhiked right across country.
-别说了 -对不起
- Stop! - Sorry.
麦克，如果让你许一个愿、望…
Mike, if you had one wish right now...
你最想要什么？
one thing, what would it be?
爸爸，我现在没这个心情
Dad, I'm really not in the mood for this.
别这样，麦克 说来听听嘛
Come on, Mike. Come on, come on, come on.
如果让你许个愿、望…
I mean, if you had one thing...
一个能让你感到万分幸福的愿、望 你会想要什么？
that would make you the happiest guy in the world, what would it be?
纯金舞者
A Solid Gold dancer.
好吧，让你许两个愿、望
All right, two wishes.
要一张演唱会的前排票子
Front-row tickets to the Springsteen concert.
第7排的可以吗？
Well, would seventh-row be all right?
爸爸，你就别玩弄我的感情了
Come on, Dad. don't toy with my emotions.
亨廷顿干洗店，三件亲衫 洗净熨平不要上奖
"Huntington Dry Cleaning. Three shirts, clean, press, no starch."
谢谢爸爸 这是我第三个愿、望
Thanks, Dad. That was my third wish.
好吧，是我搞错了
Okay, okay. Sorry. Wrong pocket.
这张怎样？
How about these?
天哪
It cant be.
爸爸，你知道这是什么吗？
Dad, do you know what these are?
-斯普林斯丁的演唱会门票! -真的？
- These are Springsteen tickets! - Really?
真不敢相信，你怎么弄到的？
I cant believe it. How did you get them?
我今天和你妈作了个决定
Well, Mike, your mom and I made a big decision.
要么花钱让你念大学 要么拿来买这些票子
We could either afford to send you to college or we could get those tickets.
-你觉得怎样？ -你选择得太对了
- What do you think? - I think you made the right choice.
太棒了，两张演唱会的票子
I cant believe it. Two tickets to Springsteen.
杰里知道的话肯定会发疯的
Wait till I call Jerry. He's gonna freak.
等一下，可怜可怜他吧
Hey, wait a minute. Show some compassion.
杰里知道我们去看的话 肯定会气死的
When Jerry finds out we're going, it's gonna kill him.
不必再刺激人家啦
We don't want to rub it in.
没错…
Right, right.
麦克，你不介意和爸爸一起 去看演唱会吧？
Hey, Mike, you don't really mind going to the concert with your old man?
不…
No. No.
真的吗？
You sure?
是的，这简直棒极了
Yeah. Dad, this is going to be great.
你不想跟你的哥们一起去吗？
I mean, you don't want to take one of your buddies?
不
No.
-想带杰里去吗？ -不
- You want to take Jerry? - No.
-佩姬.泽琳斯基呢？ -不
- Peggy Zelinsky? - No.
爸爸，我想和你去，真的
No, Dad, I want to go with you, really.
好啊，咱们打电话去气气杰里
Well, all right, then. Lets call Jerry and rub it in.
开个玩笑
Just kidding.
我发誓，哥们，我已经想尽办法了 但就是搞不到票
I swear it, man. I have tried everywhere. There is not one more ticket around.
麦克，你弄到票了吗？
Hey, Seaver, did you score tickets?
我有说过要去弄票吗？
Hey, did I say I was gonna score the tickets?
瞧这个
Voila.
太棒了，哥们 你从哪搞来的票？
Outrageous, man! Where did you get these?
我自有门路
I have my connections.
小迈，伙计，好哥们
So, Mikey. Buddy. Broski.
你弄到了多少张票？
Just how many tickets you got here?
就两张
Just two.
你以为他会带上你吗？靠边站吧
What? You think hes gonna take you, bonehead?
你会带我去的，对吧，麦克？
Hes gonna take me, right, Mikey?
恕我爱莫能助了，哥们
Sorry, guys. No can do.
好吧，我能理解 你肯定是请…
Okay. Okay, I can respect that. Now let me guess.
佩姬.泽琳斯基去，对吗？
Peggy Zelinsky, right?
伙计，这可是个好机会哦
Oh, man, what an opportunity.
你见过女孩子看完 演唱会后的样子吗？
Have you ever seen a girl after a Springsteen concert?
她们全变成了疯狂野兽
They turn into wild animals.
-你邀请她了吗？ -还没有
- Have you asked her, yet? - Well, no, not exactly.
佩姬喜欢我，但她对我没吸引力
I mean, Peggy wants me, man, but she just doesn't do it for me.
我的英语要迟到了 先走一步
Look, I'm gonna be late for English. Gotta go.
“我的英语要迟到了”
"lm gonna be late for English. Gotta go."
麦克，你的英语也太烂了
Come on, Seaver, you barely speak English.
你究竟要带谁去？
Who are you going with, man?
“沃巴巴”
Mafuther.
谁？
What?
-“沃巴巴” -沃巴巴是谁？
- Mafuther. - Who's Mafuther?
是不是那个新来的巴基斯坦同学？
Wait. Is that that new weird kid from Pakistan?
不，我是和我老爸一起去
No, man. I'm going with my father.
你要和你老爸去看演唱会？
You're gonna go see Springsteen with your father, man?
我老爸可不像一般的父亲
Hey, look, my fathers not like a father, okay?
他可是个很前卫的人
Hes a cool guy.
是很前卫，上次我去他家时…
Yeah, hes cool. Last time I was over there...
他爸正边给地板打蜡 嘴里边哼着
he was waxing the floor and singing Puff the Magic Dragon.
别在这里胡说，波纳
don't be a jerk, all right, Boner?
老实说，麦克 这样太奇怪了
I'm telling you, Seaver, it's weird.
有什么好奇怪的？
Look, it's not weird, okay?
你不和自己老爸出去 是你自己傻冒
Just because you're too big a jerk to do anything with your father...
这并不代表我这样做不正常
doesn't mean there's anything weird or un-cool about it.
再说三道四我就要你们的命
You guys breathe a word of this to anybody and you're dead meat.
★你开不了手中枪
You can't start a fire
★不扣扳机你开不了手中枪
You can't start a fire without a spark
★这支枪专供出租
This gun's for hire
今晚最有趣的是 观众群里有各种年龄段的人
One fascinating aspect of tonight's crowd is its broad age range...
如果我没猜错的话…
and if I'm not mistaken...
今晚的演唱会 吸引了好几代观众前来
evidence of this cross-generational appeal is right here.
请问一下，年轻人
Excuse me, young man.
你是和你父亲来看演唱会的吗？
Did you attend this evenings concert with your father?
有谁会关心？
Who wants to know?
亲爱的观众朋友 这里是纽约新闻节目
All of the Tri-State area. This is Newsline New York.
-先生，他是你儿子吗？ -这个大小伙子？
- Sir, is this your son? - Hey! The big fellow here?
他不仅是我儿子 还是我最好的朋友
Not only is this my son, this is my best buddy.
你认为父子一起来 听摇滚乐演唱会…
Tell me, sir, isn't it unusual for a father and a son...
是否是件不寻常的事情？
to attend a rock "n" roll concert together?
当然不是，在我们家很正常
No, no way. No, not in our family.
我们彼此有着深厚的感情，对吗？
Not in any family that loves each other. Right?
布鲁斯…我们爱死他了
Bruce, Bruce. We loved it.
年轻人，你想和你的同学说几句吗？
Young man, anything you'd like to say to your friends at school?
凯罗，我刚才到阁楼去了
Carol, I was just upstairs in the attic.
太棒了，妈妈
Hey, that's great, Mom.
奶酪没有了，捕鼠夹也闭上了 但却没有老鼠的影子
All the cheese is gone and all the traps are sprung, but there's no mice in them.
是吗？
Really?
凯罗，我和老鼠并没有私人来恩怨
Carol, I have nothing personal against these mice.
但我孩子们的健康要比老鼠更重要
It's just that my children's health is more important to me than theirs is.
好吧
Fine!
你尽管杀光它们吧…
Just go ahead and kill them...
但什么时候是个头呢，妈妈？
but where does it stop, Mom?
今天是老鼠 明天是邻居家狂叫的狗…
Today it's mice, tomorrow it's the neighbors barking dog...
说不定哪天就轮到邮递员了
then maybe the mailman's late one day.
杀害邮递员可是件人命案，妈妈
Killing a mailman is a federal offense, Mom.
她的反应还不算过激
Well, at least she didn't overreact.
麦克，演唱会…
Hey, Mike. How was the...
怎么样了？
concert?
孩子们今天怎么都气乎乎的？
Is there an irate children's convention upstairs?
怎么了？
What?
麦克怎么了？
What's with Mike?
我怎么知道？
How should I know?
回来的路上他一句话也不说
Didn't say a word to me all the way home.
Oh?
也许是他觉得我让他出洋相了
I guess he thinks I embarrassed him or something.
为什么？你干什么了？
Why? What did you do?
我什么也没干 他反应过敏而已
I didn't do anything. He's overreacting.
刚才看完演唱会时 电视台采访我们…
We got interviewed by a television crew down there, and....
算了
Never mind.
我不想再谈了
I'd really rather not talk about it.
事情总会过去的…
Oh, well, I'm sure it'll blow over...
明天之前…
by tomorrow...
要么就后天
or the next day.
你好啊，电视大明星
So, how's my brother, the big TV star?
别说了，凯罗 我今天倒霉透了
Hey, knock it off, Carol. I've been getting that all day.
大家好，这里是纽约新闻
Hello, everybody, this is Newsline New York.
在我身旁的是麦克和简森 这两个非常有趣的父子
Were here with Mike and Jason Seaver, two really cool guys.
南茜星期六不肯和我去看电影 知道我怎么做的吗？
Nancy wouldn't go with me to the movies Saturday, so you know what I did?
-怎样？ -我叫了我老爸去看
- What? - I asked my dad.
波纳，这没什么好乐的
Hey, Boner, you're a real funny guy.
小迈，听我说…
Hey, Mikey, listen.
你跟你爸，我跟我爸 来次双档怎么样？
Maybe you and your dad could double with me and my dad some night.
小迈，跟我们说说…
Mikey, you can tell us.
约会有进展吗？ 还只是跟人家道了声晚安？
Did you get lucky, or was that good night kiss all you got?
你俩把脑叶切除后 果然变得有趣了
You guys are a lot funnier since your lobotomies.
瞧这一家子
What a family.
儿子和老子约会 现在妹妹又站出来为哥哥辩护
The guy dates his dad, then gets his little sister to stick up for him.
这到是件新鲜事哦
You know, this could make the news, too.
我们是朋友，我爱死这小子了
What a guy. Were buddies. I love this guy!
[救救老鼠] 快来，本
Come on, Ben.
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
老鼠需要你的帮忙
The mice need your help.
本人不过问政治
lm just not political.
本…
Ben...
现在有个原则问题 需要我们选择自己的立场
there comes a time when principle alone compels us to take a stand.
-我给你两毛五 -一块
- Ill give you a quarter. - A dollar.
-五毛 -救助老鼠
- Fifty cents. - Save the mice.
救救老鼠，反对杀生
Save the mice. Release the rodents.
好了，凯罗，你胜利了
Okay. Okay, Carol, I give up. You win.
拿去吧
Here.
“平等自由的老鼠旅馆”
"Born Free Mouse Hotels.
“老鼠进去之后，你要为它找到更合适的 生态环境它才会出来”
"Your mouse checks in and doesn't check out...
"until you find him a more suitable enviroment."
还不止这些呢
And that's not all.
简森，跟凯罗说说这些幸运的老鼠 赢得了什么
Jason, tell Carol what these lucky mice have won.
麦姬，这些幸运老鼠 除了能保住性命之外…
Well, Maggie, in addition to having their lives spared...
还将受到全程护送 免费进行为期两周的休假
our furry little friends will be whisked away for a fun-filled, all-expense-paid...
地点是迪斯尼乐园
two-week vacation to Disneyland.
它们将会在那里遇到老鼠之王 你们猜会是谁…
Yeah, where they will meet the big cheese himself, you guessed it:
就是米老鼠
Mickey Mouse.
别逗我了
You guys.
嘿咻…
Boy, oh boy, oh boy.
就是说我们也去迪斯尼乐园？
Does this mean were going to Disneyland, too?
不
No.
这么晚了，麦克上哪去了？
It's getting late. I wonder where Mike is.
你去图书馆找，我去博物馆找
You check the libraries. Ill check the museums.
真不明白他为什么这么小题大做
Why is he making such a federal case out of this?
昨晚一整晚不和我说话
You know, he didn't speak to me last night.
今天又对我很冷淡 到现在还没回来
He gave me the cold shoulder this morning. Now hes two hours late.
简森…
Jason, Jason, Jason.
我认为在目前的情况下 对生活你最好是朝前看
I find that at times like these, it's good to keep a little perspective on things.
亲爱的，他现在的情绪肯定好转了
Honey, I'm sure he's over it by now.
话说回来，我不是心理医生
On the other hand, I'm no psychiatrist.
先失陪了 我得去安置那些小老鼠了
If you'll excuse me, I have to go tuck in the mice.
这只鼻子很像你母亲
You did get your mothers nose.
好吧，对不起 就当这是个傻玩笑吧
Okay, sorry, dumb joke.
不，你的确是个 很风趣的人，爸爸
No, no. You're a laugh riot, Dad.
麦克…
Hey, Mike...
对不起了，好吗？
I am sorry, okay?
我知道我让你难堪了，对不起
I know you feel I embarrassed you, and I'm sorry.
-没什么，爸爸 -麦克…
- Yeah, sure. Great, Dad. - Mike...
我向你道歉了
lm apologizing.
难不成你还要我公开道歉吗？
don't you think we should get this out in the open?
难道你想上国家电视台？
What, you mean like on national television?
我花了很多钱才买到那两张票…
You know, I paid a lot of money for those tickets...
都是为了让你去看那场演唱会
and that was so you could go to the concert.
我觉得你有点太顾着自己了…
I think you're being a little self-absorbed about--
我太顾着自己？
lm being self-absorbed?
爸，你在晚间新闻里让我出了洋相
Dad, you gave me noogies on the evening news.
有的父母把自己的儿女 关在家里长达7年
Well, some peoples parents lock them in a closet for seven years.
你算好的了 有老爸这么疼你
You got it real rough. Your father likes you.
还说什么难堪，出洋相
Gross, cooties!
我当时是在表达我对你的情感，麦克
I was showing my feelings for you, Mike.
你对妈妈也有情感…
You got feelings for Mom, too...
难道你也会当着电视观众的面 表达出来？
but you don't go showing them in front of whole Tri-State area.
爸，你不知道 我的那些同学…
Dad, you just don't know. I mean, the guys at school--
行了，麦克 你那么在乎他们的话干嘛？
Come on, Mike, what do you care what those guys say?
爸，你这话说得轻巧 你体会不到那种心情的
Dad, it's easy for you to say. You don't.... You just don't know what it's like.
他们都在笑话我跟你一起出去
I mean, they laughed at me because I went with you...
我为你辩护 我说“我爸是个沉稳的人”
but I defended you. I said, "My dads a cool guy."
而后你的表现呢？
And then what did you do?
你当众对我左亲右抱
You slobber all over me on Newsline New York.
好吧，麦克，对不起
All right. Okay, Mike, I am sorry.
也许我们不该一起去看演唱会
Maybe we shouldn't have gone to the concert together.
我不是这个意思
Hey, that's not what I'm saying.
也许你该约个女孩一起去
No. I mean, maybe you just should have taken a girl.
爸，你并没理解我
Dad, you're not listening to me.
Look...
我说这话是冒着很大风险的
lm taking a big risk by telling you this...
我是很喜欢和你一起去玩
but I actually like doing stuff with you.
我想和自己老爸去看 斯普林斯丁的演唱会
I do. I mean, l was sitting there watching Springsteen with my dad...
许多人的父母 连斯普林斯丁都不知道呢
and a lot of other people's parents don't even know what a Springsteen is.
整个演唱会我一直在想 “这真是太棒了”
And all through the concert I was thinking, "Hey, you know, this is really great."
就这样
Yeah.
我当时的想法跟你差不多
Well, you know, I was thinking pretty much the same thing.
也许我们都有一种共同的想法
Well, maybe there's a way that we can both think that...
就是不想让外人来干扰这一切
without letting the entire free world in on it.
我当时也许是有点失控了
Well, I guess l did lose control a little.
是很失控
Okay, a lot.
没关系了，爸爸
That's all right, Dad.
摇滚乐是让人有点兴奋
I guess Bruce has that effect on people.
也许我们下次就该听些 柔和点的音乐
I guess maybe next time we should see someone a little less dynamic.
我听说“奥斯蒙兄弟”要来这里演出了
Well, I hear the Osmonds are coming to town.
我爱死他了
I love this guy.
告诉你们，看和听简直是两码事
You guys, I'm telling you, this does not compare with seeing him live.
麦克…
Mike! Mike!
你妈妈和我正在隔壁房间看书
Your mother and I are in the next room. Were trying to read.
能不能把那玩意儿关小声点
You guys think you could turn down that....
关小声点就是了
Turn down whoever that is.
[zeroxia@gmail.com] 2006.03.07